How far will you go for one more look?
The Voyeurs is a thriller film directed by Michael Mohan.
When Pippa and Thomas move into their dream apartment, they notice that their windows look directly into the apartment
opposite – inviting them to witness the volatile relationship of the attractive couple across the street.
But what starts as a simple curiosity turns into full-blown
obsession with increasingly dangerous consequences.
Pippa, played by Sydney Sweeney.
Thomas, played by Justice Smith.
Seb, played by Ben Hardy.
Julia, played by Natasha Liu Bordizzo.
Ari, played by Katharine King So.
Joni, played by Cameo Adele.
The Voyeurs is a 2021 American erotic thriller film
written and directed by Michael Mohan.
Shot and set in Montreal, Quebec, Canada, it stars Sydney Sweeney and Justice Smith as a young couple who spy on and
become obsessed by the lives of their neighbors across the street (Ben Hardy and Natasha Liu Bordizzo).
Greg Gilreath and Adam Hendricks serve as producers
under their Divide/Conquer banner.
The film was released by Amazon Studios on Amazon
Prime Video on September 10, 2021.
Despite receiving mixed reviews from critics, the film's streaming
performance exceeded Amazon Studios' expectations.
The film explores themes of infidelity, sexual
obsession, espionage, photographer, eroticism.
The tone is emotional and intense.